#### Contact

drumatey@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/andrew-matey-37b1b798 (LinkedIn)

#### Top Skills

Healthcare Hospitals ICU

Certifications
CCRN

# **Andrew Matey**

Director of Critical Care APPs, ACNP at Grady Health System Mableton, Georgia

#### Summary

Experienced Critical Care APP, specializing in Cardiovascular ICU. Currently serving as the Director of Critical Care APPs at Grady. Responsible for developing the APP program at Grady and implementing/overseeing APPs (NPs and PAs) for MICU, CVICU, Surgical Trauma ICU, and Trauma.

## Experience

Grady Health System
Director of Critical Care APPs, ACNP
November 2017 - Present (2 years 8 months)

Responsible for developing & directing the critical care APP program at Grady Health System, which covers Grady-employed APPs operating within MICU, CVICU, Surgical-Trauma ICU, and Trauma.

Piedmont Atlanta Hospital Acute care nurse practitioner March 2015 - April 2018 (3 years 2 months) Piedmont Atlanta

CVICU/Critical Care NP

Cancer Treatment Centers of America Acute Care Nurse Practitioner August 2016 - February 2018 (1 year 7 months) Newnan, Ga

Medical ICU/Critical Care NP

Southern Grace Hospice & Palliative Care Nurse Practitioner March 2016 - March 2017 (1 year 1 month) McDonough, Ga

Part-time NP performing recertification assessments

Emory Healthcare ICU Agency Nurse 2013 - January 2015 (2 years)

Grady Health System RN surgical/trauma ICU 2011 - January 2015 (4 years)

## Education

Emory University

MSN with concentration in Acute Care, Acute Care Nurse Pracitioner 
Graduate 12/14 · (2013 - 2014)

Georgia State University

Bachelor's Degree, Registered Nursing/Registered Nurse · (2008 - 2011)